projecthoneypot.org 2019-03-21

# Privacy Policy | Project Honey Pot

## Project Honey Pot Privacy Policy

As part of Project Honey Pot, Unspam will not sell, rent, or give away any of your personal information without your consent. It is our overriding privacy principle that any personal information you provide to us is sacrosanct. We do not presume that you are granting us permission to share your personal information with third parties wanting to sell you products or services that you have not requested. In order for us to provide some of the services we do we may on occasion need to provide information you supply us to external parties. When this is necessary we will provide you explicit notice and the ability to opt-out. Unspam may need to purge information from its system from time to time, and does not promise to keep any information beyond what is required by applicable law or regulation.

### INFORMATION DESIGNATED AS PUBLIC

As part of our service you may decide to provide information specifically to be shared with third parties. For example, you may donate an mail exchanger record (an "MX Record") and give us permission to use it to create honey pot addresses on third party websites, or you may install a honey pot on your website and allow us to build statistical reports based on what spiders harvest it. In cases such at these, we will try to make it clear whenever any information you provide us will be made public. Even when you give us permission to make certain information public, we will still protect the information designated private (such as your name, email address, zip/postal code, IP address, etc.) from being disclosed.

### INFORMATION COLLECTION

Unspam is the sole owner of the information collected on this site and through any Project Honey Pot-generated address. As visitors browse our web site, or messages are sent to honey pot addresses, we sometimes track them in order to provide a better service.

### CORRECTIONS TO PERSONAL INFORMATION

This web site makes it easy to correct any mistakes in your personal information at any time. Whenever possible, we will give you an opportunity to review and change any information you provide to us. If you notice a mistake in the information you provide us, you can always revise it. This can be done either online or contacting us directly.

### COOKIES

Our site uses "cookies" in order to provide a better service to our users. Cookies are placed by your browser on your computer's hard drive to assign a unique identification for your computer. Unspam never stores information we consider personal or private in a cookie. This eliminates the chance of other sites reading our cookies and learning your personal or private information. Instead, we use cookies to help direct you to the appropriate part of our web site. For example, a cookie may indicate that you are a repeat visitor to our site. We will then use that information to present you with more informative pages customized to your preferences. Our goal is to use cookies in order to provide a personally customized and easy-to-use service.

If you do not want Project Honey Pot, Unspam or other websites to use cookies, you can disable them within your browser. Some portions of the Project Honey Pot website are still functional without cookies. If you'd specifically like to delete all cookies Project Honey Pot has placed on your browser, click here. Be aware that this will reset your session, disable auto-login, and may adversely affect other functions on the Project Honey Pot website.

### DATA AGGREGATION

Unspam may aggregate data we acquire about the anti-spam industry. For example, we may assemble data to determine what honey pot addresses receive the most messages, or what statistics are of the most interest to our users. If we assemble this sort of data and provide it to external parties, your personal information (such as your name, email address, zip/postal code, IP address, etc.) will never be attached to or included in the aggregated data. Please note, public data you provide us, such as donate MX Records, may be included in the aggregate data, reports and statistics.

### PROMOTIONAL PARTNERS

From time to time, Unspam may notify you about an offer from one of our promotional partners via our website. While we may target particular types of users for these offers, we will do all of the targeting within our system. Our business partners will not have any access to the targeting information, including the names of the people who may be interested in a particular product or service. Until you affirmatively respond to a promotional offer, we will not reveal any identifying information about you to any of these partners.

### THIRD PARTY WEBSITES

The Project Honey Pot website and the other websites owned by Unspam Technologies, Inc contain links to the sites of third parties. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these external sites. We encourage users to be aware when they leave our website, and to read the privacy statements of other websites. We cannot guarantee that these third parties abide by the privacy principles outlined here.

### COURT ORDERS

It is possible that Unspam may be required by court order to provide information contained on our website. Unspam may also be required to provide information pursuant to law, applicable regulation, subpoena or other legal process. If we are ever required to provide information under these circumstances, we will, whenever possible, inform all users whose information we are compelled to reveal.

### NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES

We will always maintain the overriding principle that we will not sell, rent, or give away any personal information you share with us without your consent. We do not believe we will need to change that principle going forward. However, if we do need to change any other aspect of the policy, we will post changes on the website.

_August 9, 2004_
